

Brian Gonzalo Céspedes

Career Summary

Brian is a Full Stack developer with 4 years of experience in building and maintaining websites and mobile applications using technologies like React JS, PHP, Node JS and Java. He led a front end team and he took part in several projects applying a Scrum methodology.

Summary of Qualifications

Proficient In:

- React JS
- PHP
- Javascript
- HTML5
- CSS3
- Node IS
- lava

- Python
- Symfony
- Diango
- Mysql
- PostgreSQL
- Oracle
- WebSocket

- Android
- Redux
- Git
- Scrum

Languages

Spanish (native speaker)

English (basic)

Career History

Snappler, La Plata, Argentina

Oct. 2019 - Sep. 2020

Ssr. Frontend Developer

Brian led the front end team on a tourism project that provides lodging, tours, transfers and packages.

He also took part in other projects developing landing pages and doing maintenance of web applications.

He worked developing codes, choosing the optimal tools that fit the project, reviewing the teamwork and promoting better practices.

• Key technologies: React JS, Ant desgin, Material UI, Redux, Sagas, Styled Components.

OPSI, La Plata, Argentina

Jan. 2020 - Sep. 2020

Ssr. Full Stack Developer

Brian created and developed a multi-enterprise web accounting system. In this system, users can upload invoices and easily manage their financial, clients and providers information.

He .

 Key technologies: React JS, Ant desgin, Redux, Sagas, Syled Components. PHP, Synfony, Oracle.

Monitoring Station, La Plata, Argentina

Jan. 2017 - Oct. 2019

Ssr. Full Stack Developer

As a Semi Senior developer, Brian worked redesigning a Monitoring System web application architecture. In addition, he developed three mobile Android apps for managing jobs, claims, invoicing, etc.

For these native Android applications, Brian used Java (frontend), Node JS (backend) and real time database (Firebase)



 Key technologies: PHP, Backbone JS, PostgreSQL, Java, Node JS, Firebase Realtime Database.

Jr. Full Stack Developer

Brian started doing the maintenance of the company's web application including administrative, commercial and technical task in order to achieve experience and improve his performance.

He worked developing frontend app modules using Backbone JS and a Backend REST API using PHP.

• Key technologies: PHP, Backbone JS. JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, PostgreSQL.

Education UNLP, La Plata, Argentina
Systems degree

Jan. 2013 - Present